enhancv.com 2019-07-08

# Privacy Policy

Last updated: May 23, 2018

##### Table of contents:

  * Introduction
  * Usage information
  * Log information
  * Account information
  * Billing information and Payment details
  * Contact information
  * Sensitive information
  * Cookies
  * How do we protect your personal information?
  * Your legal rights
  * Can this Privacy Policy change?

##### Introduction

Resumes are deeply personal documents which reveal a lot about you. Enhancv values your privacy, so we've developed an easy to understand Privacy Policy that covers how we collect and use your information.

Depending on your relationship with Enhancv, this info may include usage information, log information, account or billing information, payment details, contact information. You can understand when we collect and how we treat each type of data in the sections below.

When we refer to “we” and “us”, we mean Enhancv Ltd. which controls the information collected when you use our services on the Enhancv platform (also called "service", “product” within this document) to create your resume (or, as better known in other parts of the world, a CV) or any other document.

Keep in mind we never share the information you provide with third parties, except for chosen partners that are used for the purpose of providing you with a stable and enjoyable experience when using Enhancv. We have tried to outline here the main points of how these partners and third party services collect and use data, but for the most detailed and up-to-date information you should review their own privacy policies.

You always remain in control of your data. You may edit or erase your data from our services at any time or ask us to update or erase information we store, as long as this erasure is not in conflict with any legal obligations we may hold to national and international regulators.

By providing us with your data, you warrant to us that you are over 13 years of age. If this is not the case, you need to contact us immediately to delete any personally identifiable information from our records.

Depending on your relationship with Enhancv, we’d collect different types of information, as outlined below.

##### Usage information

What is it?

When visiting one of our domains, we will collect information about your interaction with the site, like pages you visit and specific actions you take like signing up or sharing one of our [resume examples.](https://enhancv.com/resume-examples/)

When using the Enhancv platform for creating your resume, we will collect information about the way our platform is used, including features used, resume sections used, number of resumes created, design elements used, etc. All information you knowingly include in your resume, including email, address, telephone number, is also stored in our database.

This information is collected in combination with data like user location, Internet browser type, device, operating system, your language preference, or the referring website you came to us through.

If, during the usage of Enhancv, you decide to take advantage of our Invite Friends feature and decide to invite friends by email, we will collect and store the email addresses of those friends in order to show you whether they have subscribed through your link or not, to provide you with the option of resending the invitation and to remind you which of your friends you’ve already invited. In all other cases when using the feature (e.g. sharing the link on social media or as a link in direct messaging platforms), we will only collect referral data, showing us a person came through your invite link, so that we can assign your earned credit.

How do we use it?

Usage information is used primarily in aggregate for statistical purposes. It helps us understand which parts of our product are of greatest interest and also provides information used to improve our platform and develop exciting new features. This information is shared with our third-party analytics services (including [Google Analytics](http://analytics.google.com/), [Amplitude](http://amplitude.com/), [Intercom](http://intercom.com/) and [Attribution App](http://attributionapp.com/)). Those services operate either within the EU or in accordance with the [EU-US Privacy Shield](https://ec.europa.eu/info/law/law-topic/data-protection/data-transfers-outside-eu/eu-us-privacy-shield_en), ensuring the secure transfer of information.

Resume content is stored for the purpose of providing you with the primary service of Enhancv - creating, storing, displaying, and rendering your resume. This information is stored in JSON format in [mLab](https://mlab.com/company/legal/privacy/) database hosting.

Information about your invited friends is sent to [Mandrill](http://mandrillapp.com/) for the purpose of sending out the email invitations.

Data retention

Usage information stored in [Google Analytics](http://analytics.google.com/) is kept up to 26 months after your last visit and afterwards used only in aggregate reports. Usage information in Amplitude, Intercom, and Attribution App is kept for an indefinite period of time and used only in aggregate to analyze usage patterns.

Resume content is stored for the duration of that resume being kept on our platform. If you delete your resume or delete your account, all resume content is instantaneously removed from our database.

Information about invited friends is kept within the [Mandrill](http://mandrillapp.com/) platform for 30 days after email sendout.

##### Log information

What is it?

Log data contain data about the nature of each access of our services, including originating Internet Protocol (IP) addresses and endpoint (the requested files on our platform), as well as timestamps for this activity. Web servers usually keep log files that record data each time a device accesses those servers.

We will also collect error logs which may collect more system data needed to fix known platform bugs.

How do we use it?

Log data is used to analyze platform usage, improve performance and eliminate any bugs. We primarily look at this information in aggregate, but we might review individual logs when looking for the cause of a specific issues. This may happen either by our own initiative or in relation to a request you log with our customer success team.

Only a small part of our engineering team has access to the full platform logs.

Data retention

Log data stored on our platform is kept for an indefinite period of time to help us review potential recurrence of bugs and user issues, and to monitor any attempts for unauthorised access to our services.

##### Account information

What is it?

When you create an account on the Enhancv platform, you may register with your name, email address and a password you choose. Those are stored in our platform.

If you choose to register by using a third-party account ([LinkedIn](http://linkedin.com/) or [Facebook](http://facebook.com/)), we receive your personal information (name, profile photo, email, and work experience information that can be included in your resume) from third parties if you give permission to those third parties to share your information with us. Your password for those third-party services is never shared with us.

How do we use it?

Account information is used to create your Enhancv account and identify you when logging into our platform to provide your account’s content.

Data retention

Your account information is kept during your account’s lifetime in order to identify you when logging to the platform. If you delete your account, we keep your email address in order to resolve following billing issues for the same user.

##### Billing information and Payment details

What is it?

If you are using one of our [paid plans](https://enhancv.com/pricing/), you need to provide billing information and payment details (credit card or Paypal account).

Payments are processed by [Braintree](https://www.braintreepayments.com/), a Level 1 PCI DSS compliant third-party and your credit card info is safely stored with them. Our partners never share with us payment details - we never receive your credit card or Paypal account information under any circumstances.

We analyze and review payment trends with the help of [Baremetrics](https://baremetrics.com/). Information contains name, user email addresses, information about plan types and sums paid.

How do we use it?

We use your billing information to log payments submitted as part of your plan. You can view information about all payments you’ve made to us on the [Billing page](https://app.enhancv.com/billing) of your account. You are also able to update your details whenever you need to.

Aggregate information about payments is used with statistical purposes and to execute our legitimate interest of making our business more sustainable.

Data retention

We store billing information and a full history of your payments even if you cancel your subscription or delete your account. This is part of our legal obligation to keep transaction records for local or international authorities. We also store your IP address together with your invoice data, so that we pay tax accordingly and comply with European Tax Law.

We never receive or store any payment details - they are kept with our payment partners. For further information you may refer to [Braintree’s privacy policy](http://www.braintreepayments.com/en-gb/legal/braintree-privacy-policy).

##### Contact information

What is it?

If you contact us with a question, through any of our communication channels, like our [Help Center](https://help.enhancv.com/), email, or through our social media accounts on [Facebook](https://www.facebook.com/enhancv/), [Twitter](https://twitter.com/Enhancv), or [LinkedIn](https://www.linkedin.com/company/enhancv/), we will receive and store your contact details, like email, name, or social media account link.

In the case of support queries, we might need additional information to help you with your request - this will depend on the nature of your query and issue at hand. We will aim to ask for the minimal additional information needed to solve your request.

You may also provide us with your contact details when subscribing to our newsletter or product news list. We might also collect information about categories of interests you provide us with, such as what types of content do you want to receive from us.

How do we use it?

We use your contact information to communicate regarding your query, in the case of support request, or to send you product updates and helpful materials that will help you get the most of Enhancv and create a resume you’re proud of.

Before we send you any promotional messages or content, we will collect your explicit consent for doing so. We may send you product news and updates about our latest features on rare occasions, as this is in line with our commitment for bringing value to our users, as well as our legitimate interests as service provider. You can unsubscribe from both types of communication - you will find an unsubscribe link in the footer of each promotional email we send out. You can also manage those settings from your [Enhancv Account](https://app.enhancv.com/profile). All our email communication is managed through our partners [Intercom](http://intercom.com/).

If you are a registered user of our platform, we will continue sending high priority information about your account, billing status, changes to our terms of service and other important topics. This information is an integral part of providing you our service and is managed either through [Intercom](http://intercom.com/) or [Mandrill](http://mandrillapp.com/). If you delete your account, you will stop receiving further communication from us.

Data retention

All communication history through our official communication channels between you and our team is kept in Intercom for future reference, even if your account is deleted. This is done in order to be able to answer complaints or any future questions you might have.

Contact information used for subscribing to promotional emails or product news is kept in our active subscriber lists. If you unsubscribe, we will still keep your contact information on file to prevent future email send-outs.

For all types of communication information, you can request that we delete your data and we’ll do so within a 30 day period.

##### Sensitive information

We do not knowingly collect any Sensitive Data about you. Sensitive data refers to data that includes details about your race or ethnicity, religious or philosophical beliefs, sex life, sexual orientation, political opinions, trade union membership, information about your health and genetic and biometric data. We do not collect any information about criminal convictions and offences. If you include such information as part of the content of your resume, we would still not purposefully collect and store this information or disclose to anyone.

##### Cookies

What is it?

A "cookie" is a piece of information that is stored on your computer and which records how you move your way around a website, so that when you revisit that website, it can present tailored options based on the information stored about your last visit. Cookies can also be used to analyse traffic and for advertising and marketing purposes. Cookies are used by nearly all websites and do not harm your system.

Cookies can be session-based - only stored on your computer during your web session and are automatically deleted when you close your browser - or persistent - remaining even after you close your browser. Persistent cookies are stored as a file on your computer and can be read only by the website that created them when you visit that website again.

How do we use it?

We use cookies to track your use of our website. This enables us to understand how you use the site and track any patterns with regards how you are using our website. This helps us to develop and improve our platform in response to what you might need or want.

For registered users, our platform uses cookies and HTML5 browser local storage to save your preferences and authenticate you. The third-party services we use might also use cookies, pixel tags and other similar technologies.

Cookies are also used to pursue our legitimate interests of improving marketing performance by analyzing the effectiveness of advertising and other promotional efforts.

We use cookies in [Google Analytics](http://analytics.google.com/), [Amplitude](http://amplitude.com/) and [Attribution App](http://attributionapp.com/) to analyze aggregate data for the purposes outlined above. We also cookies or pixel tags for services such as [Facebook](https://www.facebook.com/), [LinkedIn](http://linkedin.com/), or [Twitter](https://twitter.com/) in order to create and manage marketing campaigns

Deactivating cookies

You can set your browser to refuse all or some browser cookies, or to alert you when websites set or access cookies. If you disable or refuse cookies, please note that some parts of this website may not function properly. You can visit [this page](http://www.aboutcookies.org/) for more information on how to manage and remove cookies across a number of different internet browsers.

You can also deactivate specific 3rd party cookies through the [following page](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/) managed by the EDAA (European Interactive Digital Advertising Alliance).

Information and opt-out options for some common cookie providers used by us can be found here:

##### How do we protect your personal information?

Enhancv Ltd. and its authorized partners shall take appropriate organizational and technical measures to protect your Information and traffic data provided to us/them or collected by us/them, and shall not retain it any longer than permitted in order to perform its Services or as required under relevant legislation. Your personal data can only be accessed by authorized employees of Enhancv, or by Enhancv authorized partners' employees needing to access this data to fulfill their given duties.

Whenever possible, we will keep any information you provide us with limited to our own databases and systems. We may have to share your personal data in the following limited circumstances:

  * Allow our customers to pay for our Services.
  * Facilitate communication with you.
  * Manage our customer support services to you.
  * Manage our general business operation with the help of professional advisers including lawyers, bankers, auditors and insurers.
  * Abide by local and international regulations by providing information to government bodies that require us to report processing activities.
  * Track our service’s usage and provide reports to help us improve our services and conversions.

We require all third parties to whom we transfer your data to respect the security of your personal data and to treat it in accordance with the law. We only allow such third parties to process your personal data for specified purposes and in accordance with our instructions as outlined in mutual agreements and those third parties’ privacy policies.

##### How do we protect your personal information?

Under data protection laws you have rights in relation to your personal data that include the right to request access, correction, erasure, restriction, transfer, to object to processing, to portability of data and (where the lawful ground of processing is consent) to withdraw consent.

If you wish to exercise any of the rights set out above, please email us at [help@enhancv.com](mailto:help@enhancv.com).

You will not have to pay a fee to access your personal data (or to exercise any of the other rights). We may need to request specific information from you to help us confirm your identity and ensure your right to access your personal data (or to exercise any of your other rights). This is a security measure to ensure that personal data is not disclosed to any person who has no right to receive it. We may also contact you to ask you for further information in relation to your request to speed up our response.

We try to respond to all legitimate requests within one month. Occasionally it may take us longer than a month if your request is particularly complex or you have made a number of requests. In this case, we will notify you.

We may need to request specific information from you to help us confirm your identity and ensure your right to access your personal data (or to exercise any of your other rights). This is a security measure to ensure that personal data is not disclosed to any person who has no right to receive it.

##### Can this Privacy Policy change?

We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you whenever we change the policy in a material way by contacting you through email and publishing the updated privacy policy on this same URL address.

If you have any questions or concerns regarding this policy or the Enhancv service, please contact us at [help@enhancv.com](mailto:help@enhancv.com).
